A thousand million years ago, in one galactic dimension lived…
Fёdor.
One day, a mysterious witch gave him magical playing cards that he could use to summon mighty clones!
And each one of them possessed tremendous power!
Except for Brolly.
And Kuromaku.
And Spade too.
You know, now that I think about it, only one of them had powers - THE INVINCIBLE WARU!
He created a great kingdom for himself, called Waruland!
And it was a lot cooler than the others’.
Everyone wanted to get in there…
…only ‘cause you’re hogging the toilet.
Exactly!
And that’s how I gained unlimited power.
Remind me, why did we give him the bathroom?
We thought it’d be funny. It was meant to be a punishment…
And who’s laughing now? Who’s really been punished?
What the..!?
What have you done?!
We came up with a genius idea!
Again?
We divided up the apartment!
MY apartment?
We left your room untouched.
Hmm... Thank you.
You’re welcome!
What did you do!?
When you’re too busy setting up boundaries, you miss out on endless possibilities...
No, not you! The sofa!
Kuromaku, why didn’t you do anythi-...
…nevermind, I’ll sort it out.
Greetings, traveler! Come on in.
Have a taste of my sweet fruit.
Eughhh!
Hey!
And what are YOU doing?!
Barricading against the "kingdom of Felix".
Don’t be so dramatic! Where did you get those planks from?
Brolly lent me some.
Ugh, get in here! What’s the matter with you all!?
Fedya, Fedya, look, it’s done!
See here, that’s a farm, and here’s a bank, and over there are the hospitals!
You know, that is kinda cute...
IS THAT A COCKROACH?!
That’s a little resident of Felicia!
Vitalik!
Ha! Don’t be so dramatic!
My country!..
THAT IS IT!!!
I summoned you to… help me out!
But you!..
You all do the opposite!
OK, I’m calm…
LISTEN UP!
If you don’t clean up your mess, I’ll send you all…
Yes, I’ll send you!
Back to!
The card!
WORLD!
[GASP]
Get off!
You have until I get back from the store.
But you just came from there.
I’m getting supplies.
…for the pests.
He means you guys.
Aww…
You must be so sad.
Yeah.
Don’t worry, cockroaches don’t live longer than 6 months anyway.
What? WARU!
Stop horsing around, we don’t have much time.
Time is but a relative mode of being to…
That includes your quotes, Dante.
Divide the responsibilities between you, while me and Brolly, since we had nothing to do with this mess,
tidy up Fёdor’s room.
Welp, let’s get to it!
Spade! Would you fix the balcony?
Nope.
How about taking your wall down?
As in you can’t, or don’t want to?
Nope.
…You're a fat antelope!
Fёdor is threatening and manipulating us.
Didn’t you threaten him with a knife recently?
THAT’S DIFFERENT!
I’d rather live in squalor than take orders.
Done!
I just took the trash out.
Aha! You obeyed Fёdor.
Don’t you want to wash your own clothes?
The only thing that can be clean is, uh… your soul.
Dante, socks can also be clean, y’know.
Romeo! There’s still space in there!
Nah-ha-huh.
You can’t mix clothes with blankets.
Why not? I’ll run the mixed cycle.
Felix, that’s not how it works.
Fine, fine. I just wanted to save us some time.
That’s… not meant to happen!
I think I messed up… Really messed up...
Nunquam errat…
I’m losing my mind…
Do you think we did the right thing, leaving them alone?
No need to worry.
Surely it can’t get any worse than- ugh! That train wreck.
Ah-huh…
Not like they could wipe the apartment off the face of the Earth.
Mhmm...
Maybe I’m… seeing things…
Or maybe not.
I’m free!
A wall!
An impenetrable wall!
Wait a minute...
AAAH!
Something touched me!
…qui nihil agit.
What?..
Where did the bubbles come from?
I’ll tell you!
Waru swapped laundry detergent with a bath foam!
[SINISTER LAUGHTER]
Behold! The era of my great Green Kingdom has begun!
It’s white.
No, it’s green.
But the bubbles are white.
Huh! Oh yeah...
And what do you suggest we do? We don’t have time to clean this up.
Let’s look at the positives.
At least the apartment looks clean now.
We can make new clothes out of bubbles.
Ew, Romeo!
What? It was just a suggestion.
Phew...
We’ll be sent back to the card world.
I said POSITIVES!
B-but it is a positive. It’s safe there…
NOOOO!
Fart show!
O-Ouch!
“To accept the freedom of others, you first need to become free yourself.”
It’s noisy up there again!
Oh, well, it’s temporary, haha. I’ve got a friend staying with me.
Has your friend got 16 legs?
[NERVOUS LAUGH]
And what’s up with that… “soap opera” upstairs?
Whole hallway is covered!
Uhm… Un momento!
You got rid of all the paint!
And cleaned the sofa!
And even dusted off the ceiling light!
You haven’t taken down Spade’s wall, but… Yeah, whatever!
Ohhh…
I was wrong about you.
Come on, let’s have dinner.
Let me just wash my hands.
Damn…
What’s wrong?
… We didn’t turn off the washer.
You what!?
Are you serious?!
No worries, I got it!
Oh, well, I guess you could color me surprised.
[LAUGH]
He’s… laughing?
He’s in hysterics!
Hah! Call an ambulance!
Guys, haha… You’re terrible.
Well, we are your clones.
Well… then I’m no better. Let’s just clean this all up.
Together.
Well, bon apple…
bon…
apple…
Whatever!
Spade, Romeo, Brolly, Waru, Felix, Dante, Kuromaku, Ga-...
Where’s Gabriel?
Out of all the twins from that flat, you are the nicest.
Thank you for your help.
I mean, Fеdya never specified which apartment needed cleaning.
Oh, change the channel.
My favorite TV show is about to start.
This is the story about how I lost… Everything I had…